{
    "id": "9318737fb8d34fe8920a2d53182a2b04",
    "title": "Present Perfect vs. Present Perfect Continuous",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ......................................... on this project for six months now.",
            "description": "Both the present perfect and the present perfect continuous can be used to talk about an action or situation that started in the past and has continued up to the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "have worked",
                "have been working",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................. to Japan.",
            "description": "The present perfect focuses on the idea of completion.",
            "answers": [
                "has gone",
                "has been going",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ......................................... mopping the floors. What should I do now?",
            "description": "The present perfect focuses on the idea of completion.",
            "answers": [
                "have finished",
                "have been finishing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We ....................................... anything from them yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have not heard",
                "have not been hearing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They .......................................... together for six years now.",
            "description": "Both the present perfect and the present perfect continuous can be used to talk about an action or situation that started in the past and has continued up to the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "have lived",
                "have been living",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................................... the shipment.",
            "description": "The present perfect focuses on the idea of completion.",
            "answers": [
                "have received",
                "have been receiving",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ...................................... for a job since she left college.",
            "description": "The present perfect continuous focuses on the idea of continuity.",
            "answers": [
                "has looked",
                "has been looking",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "At last, she ......................................... a good job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has found",
                "has been finding",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Alan ........................................ his leg.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has broken",
                "has been breaking",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You still ........................................ that job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have not finished",
                "have not been finishing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "'You look hot.' 'Yes, I ..........................................'",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have run",
                "have been running",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You ........................................... me any help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have never offered",
                "have been never offering",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}